In this video, you will learn about the updates related to the Add Thickness option settings.
All settings related to the thickness of the board are now all under the same option.
We added an option to set the direction of the thickness of the side of the board.
Below it, there are three options. You can choose whether to display the front, back, and center of the board.
To make it easier to see, we will change the style of the costume to display the thickness and the white surface of the frame.
By adjusting the thickness of the thickness, you can increase or decrease the thickness of the side of the board.
There are three settings for the direction of the squeeze, front, back, and center of the board.
When choosing the front, the thickness of the side of the board will be squeezed forward based on the front of the board.
When choosing the center of the board, it is the same as the previous version.
It is the same as the front and back of the board.
When choosing the back, the thickness of the side of the board is squeezed backwards based on the back.
In the direction of the squeeze, you can choose whether to display the front, back, and center of the board.
When you cancel the front option, the front grid of the selected board will no longer appear.
Similarly, if you cancel the back option, the back grid will be hidden.
When you select the cross section option, the grid surface of the original hidden cross section position will be displayed.
In the edge bend ratio option, you can set the bend ratio, segment quantity, and double layer performance.
Segment quantity will affect the layout of the side grid.
The higher the value, the more detailed the side grid, the more natural the transition will be.
Although the bend ratio value can be set to high or low, when the segment quantity on the side is very low, it will not be able to provide enough bend effect.
In the end, the side will become a cut surface with no curve.
Therefore, in order to ensure the circular effect on the side, please increase this value.
When the double-sided display is turned on, the side will become a double-layer structure effect.
Thank you for watching. See you in the next video.